<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Comic Book Characters List</string>

    <string name="placeholder">placeholder</string>

    <string name="details_publisher_title">Publisher: %1$s</string>
    <string name="details_description_label">More about the character:</string>
    <string name="details_back">← GO BACT TO THE LIST</string>

    <!-- Transition names -->
    <string name="extra_list_object">LIST_OBJECT</string>
    <string name="transition_image">transition:IMAGE</string>
    <string name="transition_title">transition:TITLE</string>

    <!-- List items details below-->
    <string name="list_item_name_batman">Batman</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_superman">Superman</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_spiderman">Spider-man</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_punisher">Punisher</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_sandman">Sandman</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_wonderwoman">Wonder Woman</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_laika">Laika</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_drmanhattan">Dr. Manhattan</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_black_canary">Black Canary</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_iron_man">Iron Man</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_green_lantern">Green Lantern</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_deadpool">Deadpool</string>
    <string name="list_item_name_green_arrow">Green Arrow</string>

    <string name="list_item_publisher_dc">DC Comics</string>
    <string name="list_item_publisher_marvel">Marvel</string>
    <string name="list_item_publisher_vertigo">Vertigo</string>
    <string name="list_item_publisher_image">Image Comics</string>

    <string name="list_item_description_batman">Batman is the super-hero protector of Gotham City, a man dressed like a bat who fights against evil and strikes terror into the hearts of criminals everywhere. In his secret identity, he assumes the alias of Bruce Wayne, billionaire industrialist and notorious playboy; though "Bruce Wayne" is technically his real name, this Bruce Wayne is a disguise—that of the man he would have been had his parents not been murdered before his eyes when he was no more than a mere boy.</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_superman">Superman, also known as the Man of Steel, is one of the most powerful superheroes in the DC Universe. His abilities include incredible super-strength, super-speed, invulnerability, freezing breath, flight, and heat-vision. Born as Kal-El on the dying planet Krypton, his parents Jor-El and Lara sent him in a rocket to the planet Earth where he would be the last surviving member of his race. His rocket was discovered by the kindly Jonathan and Martha Kent, who raised him as their son Clark Kent in the town of Smallville, Kansas. His upbringing provided him with strong moral values, and life-long friends Lana Lang and Pete Ross. In his secret identity he works as a reporter at the Daily Planet in the city of Metropolis. This is where he interacts with his love interest Lois Lane, and his co-workers Perry White and Jimmy Olsen. His greatest nemesis is the brilliant super-villain Lex Luthor. To preserve the memory of his home planet and provide him rest from his double-life and adventures, he maintains a Fortress of Solitude at the North Pole. Superman remains proud of his dual heritage, taking seriously the lessons of his birth-parents and his adopted parents. Although he is an alien to this world, he heavily values his humanity, and fights with conviction for truth, justice, and the American way. There are several other heroes inspired by or directly related to his legacy, including Superboy and Supergirl. He is also a member of the Justice League of America and the Legion of Super-Heroes.</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_spiderman">Peter Parker was bitten by a radioactive spider while in high school, the spider bite caused him to develop powers and abilities similar to that of a spider. He was soon able to crawl up walls and sense imminent danger, and eventually even developed his own method of creating webs to swing from. Upon the death of his Uncle Ben due to Peter\'s indifference, Peter decided that \'With Great Power there must also come Great Responsibility\', and thus became Spider-Man.</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_punisher">A 4-year Vietnam veteran, Frank Castle became a vigilante after seeing his wife and children gunned down for accidentally observing a Mafia "hit". Since then, he has devoted his life to the task of destroying organized crime wherever he finds it. Although he aids many heroes in their quests, they often come into conflict over his way of dealing with crime. </string>
    <string name="list_item_description_sandman">Dream is a fictional character appearing in American comic books published by DC Comics\' imprint Vertigo. The character is the protagonist of the comic book series The Sandman, written by Neil Gaiman. One of the seven Endless, inconceivably powerful beings older and greater than gods, Dream is both lord and personification of all dreams and stories, all that is not in reality (which, in turn, Dream may define by his existence). He has taken many names, including Morpheus and Oneiros, and his appearance can change depending on the person who is seeing him.</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_wonderwoman">Wonder Woman is an Amazon warrior princess and one of the most powerful superheroes in the DC Universe. The daughter of Hippolyta, she was given power by the Gods to fight against evil in all its forms. Although she was raised entirely by women on the island of Themyscira, she was sent as an ambassador to the world of man, spreading their idealistic message of strength and love. Wonder Woman fights crime and acts as a positive role model for women everywhere. Her equipment includes the Lasso of Truth, magic gauntlets, and an invisible jet. In the secret identity she has adopted to become closer to humanity, she is Diana Prince, a government agent for the Department of Metahuman Affairs. Wonder Woman is also a founding member of the Justice League of America.</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_laika">In the Image series \'The Manhattan Projects\', Laika works with the Russian team alongside Yuri Gagarin. She is extremely intelligent for a dog, and is able to talk. Several important decisions are left to Laika, such as the fate of Helmutt Grottrup. Laika fights with the aid of machine guns strapped to her back. She is very close to Yuri, who has promised that they will walk on Mars together.</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_drmanhattan">Jonathan Osterman was born in 1929. His father was a watchmaker, and Jon planned to follow in his footsteps. When the US drops the atomic bomb on Hiroshima, Jon is sixteen. His father, confronted with the undeniable facts of the theory of relativity, declares his profession outdated and throws his son\'s watch-making parts out the windows, urging him to instead pursue a career studying nuclear physics. The incident represents the turning point in Jon\'s potential future from watchmaker to nuclear physicist and foreshadows Doctor Manhattan\'s \'exterior\' perception of time as predetermined and all things within it as so determined, including Doctor Manhattan\'s own reactions and emotions.</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_black_canary">Black Canary is a superhero vigilante who fights crime using martial arts and a sonic scream attack. She is one of the greatest fighters in the DC Universe, and also a strong tactical mind. Her costume is an attractive black outfit with fishnet stockings and blonde hair, and she is usually seen riding her motorcycle. There have been two Canaries to share the legacy. Dinah Drake was the original during World War II and the Golden Age of heroes. Her daughter Dinah Lance would take the position during the Silver Age when she grew old enough. Green Arrow fights alongside her most often as they are romantically involved. She has been a member of the Justice Society, the Justice League, Team Arrow and the Birds of Prey. Black Canary was created by Robert Kanigher and Carmine Infantino, first appearing in Flash Comics #86. (1947) Her more recognizable daughter was introduced by Roy Thomas in Justice League of America #220. (1983) </string>
    <string name="list_item_description_iron_man">Iron Man (Tony Stark) is a fictional superhero appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics, as well as its associated media. The character was created by writer and editor Stan Lee, developed by scripter Larry Lieber, and designed by artists Don Heck and Jack Kirby. He made his first appearance in Tales of Suspense #39 (cover dated March 1963).</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_green_lantern">Green Lantern is a superhero and an intergalactic police officer in the DC Universe. The weapon he wields is a power ring that translates his ideas into green energy using the strength of his willpower. He is a member of the Green Lantern Corps, an organization created by the Guardians of the Universe that has established thousands of members distributed throughout each space sector. There have been several assigned to the planet Earth in Sector 2814.</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_deadpool">Deadpool possesses great, though not unnatural, physical strength. He does possesses the strength of an Olympic level weightlifter. While the exact amount of weight he can lift isn\'t known, he is able to lift at least 420 lbs. His true upper limit is unknown, but due to his mutant heritage, it should be somewhere around 1400 lbs, and he would only have to stop there due to his forearms breaking under the weight. To date, Deadpool has lifted up to 800 lbs.</string>
    <string name="list_item_description_green_arrow">Green Arrow is a vigilante superhero who fights crime using archery, technology, and martial arts. In his secret identity he is politician and billionaire Oliver Queen, a hot-headed social activist and owner of Queen Industries. Black Canary is his long-time love interest and Speedy is his side-kick. The extended family of heroes who work with him call themselves Team Arrow. Oliver was killed in an explosion at one point and remained dead for many years until he was resurrected during the Quiver storyline. He has been a member of the Justice League and the Outsiders. Green Arrow was created by Mort Weisinger and George Papp, first appearing in More Fun Comics #73. (1941) </string>
</resources>
